Vladislav Munimaev

Senior Web Developer

CONTACT

Email

munimaev@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/munimaev

GitHub

github.com/munimaev

Address

Tbilisi, Georgia

CV Variants

GDocs or RUS

LANGUAGES

English

Upper Intermediate

Russian

Native speaker

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ES6
- Vue 2
- Vue 3
- React
- Redux
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Git
- Node

Senior Web Developer with 10+ years of experience, and I see the meaning of my work as making the life of users easier and helping them in solving their problems. The interface should be convenient, understandable, predictable, work quickly and, ideally, bring joy.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer

<u>CaaStle</u> project in <u>CloudGeometry</u> Tbilisi, Georgia

2023 - Present

- Work as Cloud Native Salesforce Developer on a CRM-system.
- Developing and maintaining a React website constructor.

Lead Front-End Developer

2021 - 2022

Arloid LTD Dubai, UAE

• Single-handedly maintained 5 internal products - four React and one Vue projects.

Lead Front-End Developer

2020 - 2021

General Electric project in <u>UpTeam</u> Saint-Petersburg, Russia

- Creation of an internal admin panel for configuring, and launching General Electric services, from scratch on Vue.
- Successfully and on time completed and handed over the project.

Middle/Senior Full-Stack Developer

2017 - 2020

<u>CaaStle</u> project in <u>UpTeam</u> Saint-Petersburg, Russia

- Development of a website builder and creating websites for renting clothes for CaaStle partners.
- Launch of more than a dozen sites for CaaStle partners, such as Banana Republic, Ann Taylor, Express and others.
- Rewriting the frontend part from Backbone to React.
- Complete transition of the backend part from Mohito to Express.

Middle Full-Stack Developer

2016 - 2017

Moxo project in <u>UpTeam</u> Saint-Petersburg, Russia

 Development of online applications for HR companies, clinics and schools, which allows to detect attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD).

Middle Full-Stack Developer

2013 - 2016

Bank Sovetsky Saint-Petersburg, Russia

Developed and supported internal web applications with PHP and JS.

Vladislav Munimaev

Senior Web Developer

COURSES

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

2024 / www.aws.training

Salesforce Certified Associate

2023 / salesforce.com

Mastering Vue 3 and Pinia

2022 / vuemastery.com

React

2021 / egghead.io

Mastering Vue 2

2020 / vuemastery.com

Official MongoDB courses

2018 / learn.mongodb.com

Angular.js

2016 / <u>learn.javascript.ru</u>

Node.js

2015 / <u>learn.javascript.ru</u>

EDUCATION

Saint-Petersburg State University

2013 - 2015

Faculty of Mathematics and Mechanics, Department of Mathematical Support and Administration of Information Systems.

Saint-Petersburg State Forest Technical University named after S. M. Kirov

2006 - 2011

Engineer majoring in Forest Management. Faculty of Forestry, Department of Forest Taxation and Forest Inventory.

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Creativity

On all projects, I always offered ideas and solutions for tasks with incomplete or inaccurate requirements.

Initiative

I make improvements to the processes. Often I take on tasks that are beyond my responsibility.

Responsibility

I will carefully double-check my tasks myself, trying to capture as many cases of using the new functionality as possible. I make sure that my changes do not break the existing logic.